Is that you, John?
是你吗,John?
Yes, speaking.
是我.
Tell Mary we'll be late for dinner this evening.
你告诉Mary,今晚吃饭我们将晚到一会儿.
I'm afraid I don't understand.
我恐怕我还不明白你的意思.
Hasn't Mary told you?
Mary没有告诉你吗?
She invited Charlotte and me to dinner this evening.
她邀请我和Charlotte今晚去吃饭.
I said I would be at your house at six o'clock,
我说过我6点到你家,
but the boss wants me to do some extra work.
但是老板想让我做点额外的工作.
I'll have to stay at the office.
我不得不留在办公室,
I don't know when I'll finish.
我不知道什么时候才能结束.
Oh, and by the way, my wife wants to know if Mary needs any help.
Oh,顺便问一问,我妻子想知道Mary是否需要帮忙.
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说些什么.
That is John Smith, isn't it?
你是John Smith,对吗?
Yes, I'm John Smith.
是的,我是John Smith.
You are John Smith,the engineer,aren't you?
你是工程师John Smith,对吗?
That's right.
对.
You work for the Overseas Engineering Company, don't you?
你在海外工程公司上班,是吗?
No, I don't. I'm John Smith the telephone engineer
不,不是.我是电话工程师John Smith,
and I'm repairing your telephone line.
我正在修理你的电话线.